so let's see if we can figure out how
the distributed last level cache works
let's say we have a process chip with 16
cores organized is a four by four mesh
like this the cores along with their
level one and level two caches and a
slice of l3 are connected like this so a
single tile here in this mesh has a core
a level one level two cache private to
that core and a slice of the shared last
level level three cash and that level
three cash is eight megabytes in size
has a 256 byte block size is 16 way set
associative and is distributed among the
slices round-robin by set number if core
zero issues a load from address one two
three four five six seven eight hex and
if this load is a missing level one and
in level two we send the level three
requests to what tile